Inventory of the Dean of the College Records, 1971 - 1997
Dean of the College Records, 1971 - 1997
Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.).
2000-63
10.0
10
The Dean of the College is responsible for addressing campus issues related to students, including academics, activities, diversity, health, and on-campus residences.
The Dean of the College Records date from the tenures of Edgar Beckham (1973-1990) and Allen Green (1994-1997).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Series 1 and 2 open. The third series contains restricted material and is closed.
Acquisitions Information
Transferred from the office of the Dean of the College in 2000. Additions to this collection were received in 2002 (2002-35) and 2011 (2011-24) but are restricted and have not been processed.
Historical Note
The Dean of the College is responsible for addressing campus issues related to students, including academics, activities, diversity, health, and on-campus residences.
Collection Overview
The Dean of the College Records are alphabetically arranged general subject files created by the office of the Dean of the College. There are two series of records, the first of which primarily relates to Edgar Beckam's term, and the second relates to Allen Green's term; however, there is much overlap between the two. The third series contains restricted records.
Series 1 contains material on a wide variety of issues related to the student body, including admissions, curricula, substance abuse, budgets, health, and institutional research. It also documents the 1985 visit of Louis Farrakhan.
Series 2 includes extensive documentation of The Great Hollow Wilderness School (1988-1995), Institutional Research projects (1973-1991), Organizations, the Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE), university facilities planning, and the Presidential Search Committee (1994-1995).
Collection Arrangement
The arrangement is primarily alphabetical, with some inconsistencies.
Online Catalog Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Beckham, Edgar F.; Green, Allen Johnson.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Administration.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Curricula.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Finance.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--History--20th century.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Students.; Universities and colleges--Administration.
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1: Dean of the College Files
  - Office of the Dean of the College, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Office of the University Registrar, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Study Habits/Skills, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Study Skills, circa 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AARB, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Student Mental Health, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Acceleration, 1985-1986, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Academic Affairs
    - Active Issues Academic, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Active Issues Administrative, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Admissions Task Force on Hispanic Students, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Affirmative Action
    - Affirmative Action Program, 1980-1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Affirmative Action General, 1984-1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Afro-American
    - Afro-American Fund, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Revolt of the Privileged [Alford A. Young book], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alcohol
    - SAC Alcohol /Drug Packet, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Alcohol Abuse, circa 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Drunken Driving, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Alcohol Policy
    - Alcohol Policy, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Alcohol, 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Trinity College: Substance Abuse and Use Conference, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Alcohol Policy-Trinity/Conn. College, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Alcohol Education Project, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Alternate Route to Certification, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Budget
    - Budget Status Report, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Capital Projects Budget 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Budget Meeting, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Financial Reports, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Budget Material, 1989-1993 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Campus Center Programs 1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - University Database, circa 1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Office of Community Services, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - COFHE, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Debating Society, 1983, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Departmental Core Activities Spring 1996 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Departmental Regulations, 1980-1992 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Dining
    - Dining, circa early 1990s (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Dining Group, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - ARA Services, circa early 1990s (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Dining Program 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Disaster Plan, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Divisional Directors, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Latin Presence on Campus, circa 1977-1983 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Multi-Cultural Affairs, 1987-1991 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Ujamaa, 1984-1987, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Drugs
    - Drug Policy, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Department of Education Drug-Free Schools Legislation, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - EPC Limited Enrollment Course Information, 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - EPC Task Force on Class Size and Access (TOSCA), 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Educational Policy Committee, 1971, 1975, 1990-1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Enrollment Data File, 1990, 1993, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Enrollment Planning, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Science Dept., circa 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Advising, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Meeting, Student Issues, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - FCRR [Faculty Committee on Rights and Responsibilities], 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Staff Changes, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Farrakhan
    - Farrakhan, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 13-14)
    - Farrakhan Letters, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Fellowships, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - FERPA (Family Ed. Rights and Privacy Act), 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Federal Regulations Act (FERPA), 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - First Year Curriculum, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Ford Foundation Grant
    - Ford Foundation Information, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Ford Foundation Grant, 1987, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - University Calendar Historical Information, 1984, 1988-1989, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Graduate BA/MA Degree Program Acceptance, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Grant Proposals, 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Great Hollow Wilderness School, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Handicapped, 1977-1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Harvard, 1981-1988 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Health Insurance
    - Student Health Insurance, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Health Insurance-Athletic, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Student Health Insurance 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Foreign Student Health Insurance, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - University Health Plan, 1988-1992 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Health Issues, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Health Insurance, Student, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Health Insurance-Title IX, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Health Education 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - History, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Hewlett File, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Homophobia, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Honor Code
    - Honor Code, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Rutgers Honor Code Study, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Honor Code Study, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Honors, 1985-1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - University Housing
    - Safety Committee, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Residential Life Staff, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Housing Office Evaluation, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Hughes Program in Life Sciences, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Personnel Committee, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Human Resources, 1986-1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Institutional Priorities Advisory Committee (IPAC), 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Employee Handbook, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Institutional Research
    - IR/Rutgers Study, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - IR Director, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - IR Curriculum Database, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - IR Faculty Database, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - IR, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - IR Steering Committee, 1985-1986, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - IR Budget Notes 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - IR Space, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - IR Preparation 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - HERI (Higher Education Research Institute), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - IR Freshman Survey 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - IR Freshman Survey, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - IR, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - IR Black Retention, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - IR Report: Limited Enrollment Courses, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - IR, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - IR Use of Curriculum, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - IR Senior Survey 1989, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - IR 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - IR Senior Attitudes, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - IR Admission Research, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - IR Faculty Compensation, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - IR EPC Study, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - IR Miscellaneous (course file, limited enrollment, etc.), 1987-1993 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Institutional Research-General, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - IR, 1985-1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Student Judicial Board, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - McNair Federal Grant (2 folders), 1986-1990 (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
  - McNair 1989 and 1992 Proposals (Box 4, Folder 6-7)
  - Pew Trust Foundation, 1987, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pew Trust Grand, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - IR: J. Polthier-Reports, Agendas, etc. (3 folders), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 10-12)
  - Wartime Issues, Visiting Artists Funding, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Pine Manor, circa 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Phys. Ed./Health Center, 1986, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Plagiarism, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Public Safety, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Public Safety, Campus Security HR3344, 1985-1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Public Safety Grievance, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Student Services: Accreditation Report, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Residential Life Report, 1988-1997 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Rights and Review Board, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Student Budget Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Chaplaincy Review Sub-Committee, 1978-1990 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Health Sub-Committee of the SAC, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Current Issues: Janina Montero Files (acting Dean of College) 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - President’s Correspondence, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - WSA: College Body Tax, 1975, 1983, 1989, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Series 2: Dean of the College Files
  - Policies
    - Work Plans, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Affirmative Actions, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Personnel/Benefits Review Committees, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Parental Leave Policy, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Dean’s Office Review, 1987-1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Academic Issues
    - Academic Advising, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Academic Calendar, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Wesleyan Academic Proposals, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Academic Regulation, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Academic Review Process, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Academic Review-Fall Semester 1994, Summaries, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Acceleration Charges, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Advanced Placement, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Blue Add Extension, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Grade Calling, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Graduation Requirements, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Historically Black Colleges and Universities, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Honors, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Major Report, 1994-1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Petitions, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Petition Review, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Prizes, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Required Resignation, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Strict Probation, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Summer Program, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Student Traffic, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Student/Faculty Issues, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Tuition-Early Graduation, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Tutoring/TA’s, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Urban Education Semester, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Surveys
    - COFHE Parents Survey, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Frosh Survey 1994 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Frosh Survey, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Governance Survey, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Senior Survey, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Ed. (COFHE) Senior Survey, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Senior Survey, 1993, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Gender Equity in Athletics, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence with Student/Parents, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Senior Survey 1992, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Student Poll-U.S. News and World Report, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Wesleyan Program in Israel, 1994, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Administration
    - Administrative Organizational Chart, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Affirmative Action, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence-University Calendar, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Class Access/Enrollment
    - Class Access/Size, 1990, 1993-1996 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Enrollment Planning, 1992-1996 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Enrollment Planning Group, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - The Size Question, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Residency Requirements, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Admission Enrollment Projections, 1993-1996 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Committees
    - ACAG (Admintrative Computing Advisory Group), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - ACAG, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Benefits Review Committee Members, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Commencement, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Communications Committee, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Disabilities Committee, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Enrollment Planning Group (EPG), 1996 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Events Committee, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Education Policy Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - New Faculty Reception, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Consortium with the Marine Biological Laboratory, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Human Resources Group Data, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - NESCAC [New England Small Colleges Athletic Conference], 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - ADA Americans w/Disabilities Compliance Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Budget Planning Group, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - CASM/AFCA, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Dining Advisory Committee, 1988, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Dining Issues, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Financial Aid Group, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Financial Aid Overview Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Financial Aid Overview Committee, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Inauguration Planning Committee, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Institutional Research Adv. Com. (IRAC), 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Information Technologies Adv. Com. (ITAC), 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
    - Telecommunications Proposals, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Giants, Wizards and Elves, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Long Lane Task Force, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Mapping the Curriculum, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - MISAA-Management Info. Academic Affairs, 1992, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Personnel Committee, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Presidential Search Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - SIPAC 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Student/Administration Relations, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Board Of Trustees
    - Board Governance, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Board of Trustees, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - FY 93-94
    - Budget Control Report FY93-94, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Operating Plan FY93-94, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - FY93-94, Year-end Analysis, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Student Services Budget, FY93/94-94/95, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Development
    - Alumni
      - Black Alumni Award, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Conversations with Alumni Program, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Annual Giving
      - Parents Reception 4/26/96, NYC, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Alumni/Parents Reception 10/6/94 Hartford, CT, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Alumni/Parents Reception 10/27/94, Philadelphia, PA, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Parents Council
      - Parents Council, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Capital Campaign
      - Ford Foundation/Diversity Grants, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Feasibility Report, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Capital Campaign: Student Services, 1991-1995 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Admissions Building, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Administrative Campaign Planning Group, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Capital Projects Planning Group
      - Capital Projects Planning Group, 1993-1995 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Capital Projects Planning Group, 1980, 1983, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Federal Regulations
    - ADA Compliance, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Financial Aid
    - Financial Aid Budget, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Budget Report, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Financial Aid Budget Report, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE), 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Pell Grant, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Financial Aid Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Financial Aid - Wesleyan, 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Fellowships
    - Mellon Minority Undergraduate Fellowship
      - Mellon Minority Fellowship, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - Mellon Foundation, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      - Mellon Survey, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Thomas J. Watson Fellowship, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Grants
    - Grant Guidelines, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Ford Foundation Diversity Grant, 1991-1995 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Hewlett Grant, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Hewlett Foundation Proposal, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Luce Foundation Professorship, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Budget, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - McNair, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - McNair Program, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - McNair Program, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Great Hollow Wilderness School
    - Great Hollow Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Great Hollow Wilderness School, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Great Hollow Wilderness School, 1988-1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Great Hollow Wilderness School, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Wesleyan McNair Program Advisory Committee Meeting, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - International Studies
    - International Studies Program, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - International Studies Program, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Life
    - Activity Issues, 1990-1994 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Havurah, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Kosher Kitchen, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Organizations
    - Association of Concerned African Scholars (ACAS), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - African Students Association (ASA), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Black Law Students Association Harvard Law School, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Historically Black Colleges and Universities (HBCU), 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - CIEE [Council on International Education Exchange], Academic Consortium Board, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - CIEE Meeting 1/28/95, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - CIEE Council on International Education Exchange, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - International Studies Program (CIEE), 1996 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Student Governance
    - CIEE Study Abroad Program, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - ASCEND [Alumni and Students Combined Enhances Natural Development], 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - SCC Students of Color Council, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - SOAR, Society Organized Against Racism in Higher Ed., ca. 1987, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - WSA, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Freeman Scholarship Working Group, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Student Services
    - Goals for Academic Year 1994-95, Office of the Dean, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Dean’s Office Goals, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Dean’s Office Directory, Admn’s Responsibilities, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Year In Review, Dean’s Office, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Division Restructuring 1996 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Career Planning Center
      - Career Planning Center, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Goals for Academic Year (CPC), 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - Annual Report (CPC), 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - Pre-Med Advising, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Campus Center A.R., 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Campus Center, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Chapel, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Community Services
      - Peer Advising, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Community Service, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Health Education, 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - FIPSE [Funds for the Improvement of Secondary Education] Grant, 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Self Defense Classes File for Al Green, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Alcohol and Drugs, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Drugs Don’t Work Program, State of CT, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Peer Education, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Sexual Abuse, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Health Services
      - Health Services, 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, Health Services, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Student/Parent, Health Services, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Goals for Academic Year, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Health Services, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Public Safety
      - Public Safety, 1993-1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Middletown Police Discrimination case 10/31/95, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Interns for Students of Color
      - Interns for Students of Color, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Organization Consultant-Jane Saltonstall, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence-Registrar, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Registration, 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, Parents/Students, Registration Issues, 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Goals for Academic Year, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Dining Issues, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Housing Conflicts, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Residential Life and Housing, 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Res. Life and Housing Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Goals for Academic Year, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - West College Proposal, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Task Force on Residential Life, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Space Allocation Committee, 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Francis J. Marsilli, Jr. Student Affairs Practicum, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Campus Voter Registration Initiative, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Community, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Tutoring Program, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - University Plan, Five Year, 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Visiting Scholars PIMMS, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - World Wide Web, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Writing Workshop, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Institutional Research
    - Institutional Research Ad Committee 3/4/87, 1987, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 42)